(punk music)
(punk music continues)
♪ London calling to the faraway towns ♪
♪ Now war is declared
and battle come down ♪
♪ London calling to the underworld ♪
♪ Come out of the cupboard,
you boys and girls ♪
♪ London calling, now don't look to us ♪
♪ Phony Beatlemania has bitten the dust ♪
♪ London calling, see
we ain't got no swing ♪
♪ Except for the ring
of the truncheon thing ♪
♪ The ice age is coming,
the sun's zooming in ♪
♪ Meltdown expected, the
wheat is growing thin ♪
♪ Engines stop running,
but I have no fear ♪
♪ 'Cause London is drowning ♪
♪ I live by the river ♪
♪ London calling to the imitation zone ♪
♪ Forget it, brother,
you can go it alone ♪
♪ London calling to the zombies of death ♪
♪ Quit holding out and
draw another breath ♪
♪ London calling and I
don't want to shout ♪
♪ But while we were talking,
I saw you nodding out ♪
♪ London calling, see
we ain't got no high ♪
♪ Except for that one
with the yellowy eye ♪
♪ The ice age is coming,
the sun's zooming in ♪
♪ Engines stop running,
the wheat is growing thin ♪
♪ A nuclear era, but I have no fear ♪
♪ 'Cause London is drowning ♪
♪ I, I live by the river ♪
(punk music)
(howling)
(howling continues)
(guitar solo)
♪ The ice age is coming,
the sun's zooming in ♪
♪ Engines stop running,
the wheat is growing thin ♪
♪ A nuclear era, but I have no fear ♪
♪ 'Cause London is drowning ♪
♪ I, I live by the river ♪
(howling)
♪ Now get this ♪
♪ London calling, yes, I was there, too ♪
♪ And you know what they said? ♪
♪ Well, some of it was true ♪
♪ London calling at the top of the dial ♪
♪ And after all this, won't
you give me a smile? ♪
♪ London calling ♪
♪ I never felt so much
alike, alike, alike, alike ♪